 {
"0": {"front": "fare", 
"back": "proceed, get along, or succeed"},
"1": {"front": "hale", 
"back": "exhibiting or restored to vigorous good health"},
"2": {"front": "firebrand", 
"back": "someone who deliberately foments trouble"},
"3": {"front": "encumber", 
"back": "hold back"},
"4": {"front": "overbearing", 
"back": "having or showing arrogant superiority to"},
"5": {"front": "rider", 
"back": "a traveler who actively sits and travels on an animal"},
"6": {"front": "pummel", 
"back": "strike, usually with the fist"},
"7": {"front": "smattering", 
"back": "a small number or amount"},
"8": {"front": "pellucid", 
"back": "transparently clear; easily understandable"},
"9": {"front": "afflict", 
"back": "cause physical pain or suffering in"},
"10": {"front": "roil", 
"back": "be agitated"},
"11": {"front": "warrant", 
"back": "show to be reasonable or provide adequate ground for"},
"12": {"front": "philology", 
"back": "the humanistic study of language and literature"},
"13": {"front": "pedantic", 
"back": "marked by a narrow focus on or display of learning"},
"14": {"front": "squeamish", 
"back": "excessively fastidious and easily disgusted"},
"15": {"front": "execrable", 
"back": "unequivocally detestable"},
"16": {"front": "deference", 
"back": "a courteous expression of esteem or regard"},
"17": {"front": "reverie", 
"back": "an abstracted state of absorption"},
"18": {"front": "enduring", 
"back": "unceasing"},
"19": {"front": "prude", 
"back": "a person excessively concerned about propriety and decorum"},
"20": {"front": "passe", 
"back": "out of fashion"},
"21": {"front": "apparent", 
"back": "clearly revealed to the mind or the senses or judgment"},
"22": {"front": "gainsay", 
"back": "take exception to"},
"23": {"front": "temper", 
"back": "a characteristic state of feeling"},
"24": {"front": "derelict", 
"back": "in deplorable condition"},
"25": {"front": "pendulous", 
"back": "hanging loosely or bending downward"},
"26": {"front": "emetic", 
"back": "a medicine that induces nausea and vomiting"},
"27": {"front": "pilfer", 
"back": "make off with belongings of others"},
"28": {"front": "institute", 
"back": "set up or lay the groundwork for"},
"29": {"front": "sinecure", 
"back": "a job that involves minimal duties"},
"30": {"front": "grandiloquent", 
"back": "lofty in style"},
"31": {"front": "placate", 
"back": "cause to be more favorably inclined"},
"32": {"front": "humble", 
"back": "marked by meekness or modesty; not arrogant or prideful"},
"33": {"front": "bemuse", 
"back": "cause to be confused emotionally"},
"34": {"front": "connotation", 
"back": "an idea that is implied or suggested"},
"35": {"front": "urbane", 
"back": "showing a high degree of refinement"},
"36": {"front": "tribunal", 
"back": "an assembly to conduct judicial business"},
"37": {"front": "cede", 
"back": "relinquish possession or control over"},
"38": {"front": "prowess", 
"back": "a superior skill learned by study and practice "},
"39": {"front": "mundane", 
"back": "found in the ordinary course of events"},
"40": {"front": "wreak", 
"back": "cause to happen or to occur as a consequence"},
"41": {"front": "disquisition", 
"back": "an elaborate analytical or explanatory essay or discussion"},
"42": {"front": "cupidity", 
"back": "extreme greed for material wealth"},
"43": {"front": "commission", 
"back": "a special group delegated to consider some matter"},
"44": {"front": "fervent", 
"back": "characterized by intense emotion"},
"45": {"front": "stump", 
"back": "cause to be perplexed or confounded"},
"46": {"front": "pacifist", 
"back": "opposed to war"},
"47": {"front": "policy", 
"back": "a plan of action adopted by an individual or social group"},
"48": {"front": "slay", 
"back": "kill intentionally and with premeditation"},
"49": {"front": "libretto", 
"back": "the words of an opera or musical play"},
"50": {"front": "onset", 
"back": "the beginning or early stages"},
"51": {"front": "stratum", 
"back": "people having the same social or economic status"},
"52": {"front": "straight", 
"back": "successive, without a break"},
"53": {"front": "assiduous", 
"back": "marked by care and persistent effort"},
"54": {"front": "wraith", 
"back": "a mental representation of some haunting experience"},
"55": {"front": "adage", 
"back": "a condensed but memorable saying embodying an important fact"},
"56": {"front": "dogged", 
"back": "stubbornly unyielding"},
"57": {"front": "exploit", 
"back": "draw from; make good use of"},
"58": {"front": "loquacious", 
"back": "full of trivial conversation"},
"59": {"front": "novel", 
"back": "an extended fictional work in prose"},
"60": {"front": "edifice", 
"back": "a structure that has a roof and walls"},
"61": {"front": "malaise", 
"back": "a general feeling of discomfort, uneasiness, or depression"},
"62": {"front": "liberal", 
"back": "having political views favoring reform and progress"},
"63": {"front": "exorbitant", 
"back": "greatly exceeding bounds of reason or moderation"},
"64": {"front": "confluence", 
"back": "a flowing together"},
"65": {"front": "imposture", 
"back": "pretending to be another person"},
"66": {"front": "odium", 
"back": "state of disgrace resulting from detestable behavior"},
"67": {"front": "repast", 
"back": "the food served and eaten at one time"},
"68": {"front": "obdurate", 
"back": "stubbornly persistent in wrongdoing"},
"69": {"front": "beatific", 
"back": "resembling or befitting an angel or saint"},
"70": {"front": "implacable", 
"back": "incapable of being appeased or pacified"},
"71": {"front": "frieze", 
"back": "an ornament consisting of a horizontal sculptured band"},
"72": {"front": "gibe", 
"back": "laugh at with contempt and derision"},
"73": {"front": "roseate", 
"back": "of something having a dusty purplish pink color"},
"74": {"front": "pervade", 
"back": "spread or diffuse through"},
"75": {"front": "dapper", 
"back": "marked by up-to-dateness in dress and manners"},
"76": {"front": "kindle", 
"back": "catch fire"},
"77": {"front": "callous", 
"back": "emotionally hardened"},
"78": {"front": "manifestation", 
"back": "a clear appearance"},
"79": {"front": "ratify", 
"back": "approve and express assent, responsibility, or obligation"},
"80": {"front": "accede", 
"back": "yield to another's wish or opinion"},
"81": {"front": "effulgence", 
"back": "the quality of being bright and sending out rays of light"},
"82": {"front": "abstemious", 
"back": "marked by temperance in indulgence"},
"83": {"front": "erode", 
"back": "become ground down or deteriorate"},
"84": {"front": "propitious", 
"back": "presenting favorable circumstances"},
"85": {"front": "cardinal", 
"back": "one of a group of prominent bishops in the Sacred College"},
"86": {"front": "insist", 
"back": "be emphatic or resolute and refuse to budge"},
"87": {"front": "sleight", 
"back": "adroitness in using the hands"},
"88": {"front": "frustrate", 
"back": "hinder or prevent, as an effort, plan, or desire"},
"89": {"front": "errant", 
"back": "straying from the right course or from accepted standards"},
"90": {"front": "traduce", 
"back": "speak unfavorably about"},
"91": {"front": "purvey", 
"back": "supply with provisions"},
"92": {"front": "discriminating", 
"back": "showing or indicating careful judgment and discernment"},
"93": {"front": "lineament", 
"back": "the characteristic parts of a person's face"},
"94": {"front": "malcontent", 
"back": "a person who is unsatisfied or disgusted"},
"95": {"front": "sextant", 
"back": "an instrument for measuring angular distance"},
"96": {"front": "expiate", 
"back": "make amends for"},
"97": {"front": "muster", 
"back": "gather or bring together"},
"98": {"front": "projection", 
"back": "a prediction made by extrapolating from past observations"},
"99": {"front": "estrange", 
"back": "arouse hostility or indifference in"},
"100": {"front": "effluvium", 
"back": "a foul-smelling outflow or vapor"},
"101": {"front": "welt", 
"back": "a raised mark on the skin "},
"102": {"front": "fresco", 
"back": "a mural done with watercolors on wet plaster"},
"103": {"front": "audacious", 
"back": "disposed to venture or take risks"},
"104": {"front": "toil", 
"back": "work hard"},
"105": {"front": "libertine", 
"back": "a dissolute person"},
"106": {"front": "ranging", 
"back": "wandering freely"},
"107": {"front": "contempt", 
"back": "lack of respect accompanied by a feeling of intense dislike"},
"108": {"front": "aggrieve", 
"back": "infringe on the rights of"},
"109": {"front": "undertaking", 
"back": "any piece of work that is attempted"},
"110": {"front": "pastoral", 
"back": "idyllically rustic"},
"111": {"front": "disconsolate", 
"back": "sad beyond comforting; incapable of being consoled"},
"112": {"front": "mortify", 
"back": "cause to feel shame"},
"113": {"front": "fulminate", 
"back": "criticize severely"},
"114": {"front": "automate", 
"back": "operate or make run by machines rather than human action"},
"115": {"front": "imperturbable", 
"back": "marked by extreme calm and composure"},
"116": {"front": "apropos", 
"back": "of an appropriate or pertinent nature"},
"117": {"front": "slew", 
"back": "a large number or amount or extent"},
"118": {"front": "prognosticate", 
"back": "make a prediction about; tell in advance"},
"119": {"front": "refractory", 
"back": "stubbornly resistant to authority or control"},
"120": {"front": "discretionary", 
"back": "not earmarked; available for use as needed"},
"121": {"front": "careen", 
"back": "pitching dangerously to one side"},
"122": {"front": "sate", 
"back": "fill to contentment"},
"123": {"front": "approach", 
"back": "move towards"},
"124": {"front": "dispassionate", 
"back": "unaffected by strong emotion or prejudice"},
"125": {"front": "codicil", 
"back": "a supplement to a will"},
"126": {"front": "unconscionable", 
"back": "greatly exceeding bounds of reason or moderation"},
"127": {"front": "rancor", 
"back": "a feeling of deep and bitter anger and ill-will"},
"128": {"front": "acme", 
"back": "the highest level or degree attainable"},
"129": {"front": "zealot", 
"back": "a fervent and even militant proponent of something"},
"130": {"front": "property", 
"back": "a basic or essential attribute shared by members of a class"},
"131": {"front": "luxuriant", 
"back": "produced or growing in extreme abundance"},
"132": {"front": "rebus", 
"back": "a puzzle consisting of pictures representing words"},
"133": {"front": "cameo", 
"back": "engraving or carving in low relief on a stone"},
"134": {"front": "ordain", 
"back": "invest with ministerial or priestly authority"},
"135": {"front": "delicacy", 
"back": "the quality of being exquisitely fine in appearance"},
"136": {"front": "conceit", 
"back": "an artistic device or effect"},
"137": {"front": "subaltern", 
"back": "inferior in rank or status"},
"138": {"front": "carrion", 
"back": "the dead and rotting body of an animal; unfit for human food"},
"139": {"front": "explicate", 
"back": "elaborate, as of theories and hypotheses"},
"140": {"front": "decadence", 
"back": "the state of being degenerate in mental or moral qualities"},
"141": {"front": "aria", 
"back": "an elaborate song for solo voice"},
"142": {"front": "practitioner", 
"back": "someone who carries out a learned profession"},
"143": {"front": "idiosyncrasy", 
"back": "a behavioral attribute peculiar to an individual"},
"144": {"front": "comport", 
"back": "behave in a certain manner"},
"145": {"front": "captious", 
"back": "tending to find and call attention to faults"},
"146": {"front": "impertinent", 
"back": "improperly forward or bold"},
"147": {"front": "sherbet", 
"back": "a frozen dessert made primarily of fruit juice and sugar"},
"148": {"front": "interpolate", 
"back": "insert words into texts, often falsifying it thereby"},
"149": {"front": "abysmal", 
"back": "resembling an abyss in depth; so deep as to be immeasurable"},
"150": {"front": "exertion", 
"back": "use of physical or mental energy; hard work"},
"151": {"front": "suspended", 
"back": " supported or kept from sinking or falling by buoyancy"},
"152": {"front": "indite", 
"back": "produce a literary work"},
"153": {"front": "brawn", 
"back": "possessing muscular strength"},
"154": {"front": "fallow", 
"back": "undeveloped but potentially useful"},
"155": {"front": "podium", 
"back": "a platform raised above the surrounding level"},
"156": {"front": "malevolent", 
"back": "having or exerting a malignant influence"},
"157": {"front": "ensue", 
"back": "issue or terminate in a specified way"},
"158": {"front": "indication", 
"back": "something that serves to suggest"},
"159": {"front": "reactionary", 
"back": "extremely conservative"},
"160": {"front": "supercilious", 
"back": "having or showing arrogant superiority to"},
"161": {"front": "despair", 
"back": "a state in which all hope is lost or absent"},
"162": {"front": "partial", 
"back": "being or affecting only a segment"},
"163": {"front": "erstwhile", 
"back": "belonging to some prior time"},
"164": {"front": "elysian", 
"back": "of such excellence as to suggest inspiration by the gods"},
"165": {"front": "venial", 
"back": "easily excused or forgiven"},
"166": {"front": "obloquy", 
"back": "a false accusation of an offense"},
"167": {"front": "hubbub", 
"back": "loud confused noise from many sources"},
"168": {"front": "crew", 
"back": "the men and women who man a vehicle"},
"169": {"front": "decorum", 
"back": "propriety in manners and conduct"},
"170": {"front": "extravagant", 
"back": "recklessly wasteful"},
"171": {"front": "flotilla", 
"back": "a fleet of small craft"},
"172": {"front": "surly", 
"back": "unfriendly and inclined toward anger or irritation"},
"173": {"front": "yield", 
"back": "give or supply"},
"174": {"front": "surreptitious", 
"back": "marked by quiet and caution and secrecy"},
"175": {"front": "hoodwink", 
"back": "influence by slyness"},
"176": {"front": "accolade", 
"back": "a tangible symbol signifying approval or distinction"},
"177": {"front": "cohere", 
"back": "cause to form a united, orderly, and consistent whole"},
"178": {"front": "cryptic", 
"back": "of an obscure nature"},
"179": {"front": "atavism", 
"back": "a reappearance of an earlier characteristic"},
"180": {"front": "endue", 
"back": "give qualities or abilities to"},
"181": {"front": "circumspect", 
"back": "heedful of potential consequences"},
"182": {"front": "ambrosia", 
"back": "the food and drink of the gods"},
"183": {"front": "banter", 
"back": "light teasing repartee"},
"184": {"front": "caucus", 
"back": "meet to select a candidate or promote a policy"},
"185": {"front": "cite", 
"back": "make reference to"},
"186": {"front": "ravel", 
"back": "disentangle"},
"187": {"front": "troth", 
"back": "a solemn pledge of fidelity"},
"188": {"front": "mendicant", 
"back": "a pauper who lives by begging"},
"189": {"front": "tide", 
"back": "the periodic rise and fall of the sea level"},
"190": {"front": "ignominious", 
"back": "deserving or bringing disgrace or shame"},
"191": {"front": "asperity", 
"back": "harshness of manner"},
"192": {"front": "imposed", 
"back": "set forth authoritatively as obligatory"},
"193": {"front": "chide", 
"back": "censure severely or angrily"},
"194": {"front": "precision", 
"back": "the quality of being reproducible in amount or performance"},
"195": {"front": "nostrum", 
"back": "patent medicine whose efficacy is questionable"},
"196": {"front": "coy", 
"back": "showing marked and often playful evasiveness or reluctance"},
"197": {"front": "pacify", 
"back": "ease the anger, agitation, or strong emotion of"},
"198": {"front": "rationalism", 
"back": "the doctrine that reason is the basis for regulating conduct"}
}
